The action of the Holy Ghost still continued, as one by one God continued to release His power and promises
into the lives of the people receiving the ministration of the anointing water.
Watch how one of the principalities contrary to this purpose was disgraced, lost his grip and was cast out
of this young man.
Who are you, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ?!
Speak, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Who are you?
Who are you in this body?
What have you done to this body?
Holy Ghost, fire!
Holy Ghost, fire all over your body!
Who are you?
I command you to speak, in Jesus' name!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
What have you done to this body?
I killed him!
Speak, in Jesus' name!
Who are you?
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
What have you done to this body?
Everything!
What have you done?
I made him small.
What else?
I destroyed him.
How have you destroyed him?
How have you destroyed him, in Jesus' name?
When did you enter him?
When he was young.
How have you destroyed him?
Rejection!
Everything!
What have you done to his family?
No love!
What have you done to his career?
He doesn't have a career.
How many of you are in this body?
Countless.
Your time has expired in this body.
Come out, in Jesus' name!
Come out, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out in Jesus' name!
Out, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
You are declared free, in Jesus' name.
Rise up.
Anointing Water Revival In The UK At The Troxy Theatre, London
How are you?
I don't have strength.
Do you know what just happened to you?
I could hear things but...
Do you know what you have just said?
No.
Jesus Christ has set you free from the demon that was tormenting your life.
Give glory to God!
I praise You, Father!
Thank You, Lord!
Thank You, Jesus!
Well, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Our brother is coming forward right now to share his wonderful testimony, to the glory of God Almighty.
One more time, let's put our hands together!
Testimony Time
My brother, it is great to have you in our midst.
Please, introduce yourself to us.
Tell us your name and where you are from.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Chris Jensen.
Originally I am from Sydney but I've been in Holland for the last two months.
You are very welcome, Chris.
Tell us first of all what were the problems that actually brought you to the Anointing Water Revival in London.
When I was 12 years old, I was clinically diagnosed with depression.
My parents sent me to many counsellors, psychologists and psychiatrists for help but nothing helped me.
I was on medication since I was 12 years old.
I am 25 now.
Tell us how this depression really affected your life and things it caused you to do.
I got panic attacks, which are like anxiety attacks that came upon me.
In high school, I would have to leave the classroom.
I couldn’t study well, function or socialise.
I would isolate myself in my room in the last few years a lot.
I was struggling.
You used to stay alone in your room, just isolating yourself?
That is correct. Yes.
Anytime you try to move out with people and be around with people - what would happen?
How would this affect you?
If I was in public, like at a restaurant or somewhere in particular,
I would have to run out because I'd have an anxiety, panic attack.
I always felt troubled inside.
So, I could never socialise or talk much.
Tell us about your dreams at this period.
What were the types of things that were happening to you in your dreams?
Sometimes, I had dreams of hanging on a rope or suicidal thoughts of death.
I dreamt of coffins.
I always dreamt that I was falling in the sky – things like that.
Apart from these dreams, physically, what were the types of thoughts that used to go through your heart,
as a result of this severe depression?
When I saw a sharp object of any kind, like a knife in the kitchen, I would have a vision or an impression
in my mind that I was stabbing myself or someone near me.
So, anytime you saw sharp objects, something would tell you to stab yourself, or someone close to you?
That is correct.
How would you restrain yourself?
I looked to the Lord and to a verse in the Word and decided I would heed to it and not do it.
You mean that right from this young age you've had these suicidal thoughts,
as well as these dreams of death?
The suicidal thoughts, visions of death and nightmares had been more recent over the last five years
but since the age of 12, it's been mainly depression and panic attacks.
We can just understand our young brother here, what he has passed through in life as a result of this situation.
Tell us, where did you go to in search of solution, when this problem was at its worst?
That's interesting.
I went to Jesus most of all.
I went deeper in my relationship with the Lord.
I sought Him in prayer and fasting and read His Word for hours.
The counsellors could not help me; medication could not help me.
So, I was looking to the Lord for a breakthrough.
Wow, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ for that faith.
In your search for deliverance; did this take you to anywhere else in the world - searching for this freedom?
That is right.
I went to Redding, California for a year to study but there was no breakthrough still, even after being there.
What did you study when you went there?
I went to the supernatural school of ministry that basically, gives you more identity in Christ
and how to walk in the things of the Spirit of God.
You even went to the Bible school, to try to draw closer to God, to get rid of this problem, but
even upon that, the problem was still there?
The problem was still there. Yes.
Well, we can just understand from our brother what he has really been passing through,
but we give glory to God that he is here, in our midst.
Tell us, how did you find out about the Anointing Water Revival and the ministry of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I have known about the ministry of T.B. Joshua for about five or six years.
How did you discover the ministry of Prophet T.B. Joshua?
I think it was through the internet on YouTube.
You were watching clips on YouTube and that's what has encouraged you
to come along to the Anointing Water Revival service?
That is right. Yes.
We just saw the clip of what happened.
Describe that experience.
Tell us exactly how you felt.
What happened when the anointing water was ministered to you.
That clip was new to me.
I had never seen that.
So, it is quite startling for me.
I don’t remember much of what happened to me but what I do recall is that when I was standing up there,
I felt quite nervous.
My teeth were cluttering together.
Then, all of a sudden, my hands felt like there was lighting, like electricity and this anger arose in me.
I can't recall what happened after that.
So, at that moment, what you saw just there...
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Chris Jenson
Anointing Water Testimony
What you saw just there, with that demonic voice speaking through you; you have no recollection of it?
No.
This is truly a wonderful deliverance that our brother received.
Once again, what we saw was not him speaking; it was evil spirit within him that had been destroying his life
behind this terrible depression, that actually was exposed by the light of God in the anointing water.
Christ, it has been 3 weeks now since your deliverance.
Just testify - what has happened to your life since then?
I no longer have that torment.
Praise God!
I've got peace.
The Prince of Peace is in my heart!
Chris Jenson
Anointing Water Testimony
A stable mind – Christ gives you the mind of His own.
So, you no longer have torment but peace – His peace.
Testimony Time
Before you said you had this terrible nightmares, there was this voice pushing you to commit suicide.
Tell us, how has been your experience, since the deliverance.
I no longer have that torment.
It is a mind that is able to think properly.
I am able to move forward.
I have the capacity to move on now.
I feel that I can socialise much better and life is going to go from glory to glory.
Amen. Let's put our hand together for Jesus Christ!
What about all those terrible suicidal thoughts; how have you been since the deliverance?
They had to go and they have definitely gone.
Praise God!
So, you no longer have that thought to stab yourself or others, when you see sharp objects?
Absolutely now, no.
This is a wonderful testimony.
How have you been sleeping since then, Chris?
Perfectly, really well.
Glory be to God!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We believe you are in a really good position to advise people of God,
especially those here waiting for their own touch.
What do you want to advise them, firstly concerning this anointing water, and also concerning the problem
you were having, and how people can get out of it?
God is bigger than your problem.
No matter how narrow the way may seem to be for you, there is a solution;
Jesus is that solution and He is going to bring you through.
Last night, before I fell asleep, I saw our Lord, Jesus Christ on His throne with many crowns on His head.
I felt that He wanted you to know that He is above all principalities,
powers and dominions and He has the answer for you today. Amen!
Praise God!
What can you say about this anointing water, that God used to set you free?
If you read the Word of God, He used many mediums to anoint with power from on high.
The anointing water is a medium to deliver you, like Jesus, Himself delivered.
So, today you are going to receive your touch through the anointing water, through Jesus Christ.
Praise God!
Lastly Chris, we know that the issue of depression, suicide is such a big problem all over the world...
You have gone through that, you have come out stronger, through Jesus Christ.
What is your advice for people out there who are going through the same problem you once had?
My advice would be that the Lord is bigger than all earthly means.
So, continue to look at the Lord, hold on to His Word and press through;
no matter what you are going through because Christ did it too.
Amen. One more time, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of all Nations.
Emmanuel TV – changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.